this place
这个地方
I stayed longer than you
我呆的时间比你长
I've only seen people coming in
我只看到有人进来
I've never seen anyone go out before
我以前从未见过有人出去
Stop wishful thinking
停止一厢情愿的想法
Run away with me
和我一起逃跑
You still have a chance
你还有机会
I'll think about it
我会考虑一下
nothing to consider
没什么可考虑的
If you stay here, you can only wait for death.
如果留在这里，就只能等死。
What you said makes sense.
你说的有道理。
Then I'll run out with you
然后我就和你一起出去
What good do I have?
我有什么好处？
what benefits do you want
你想要什么好处
Give me money
给我钱
I save your life
我救你的命
I also want to give you money
我也想给你钱
Of course you have to give me money
当然你得给我钱
I didn't need to run for the first time
我第一次不需要跑步
I know your secret now
我现在知道你的秘密了
I have to run with you
我必须和你一起奔跑
second
第二
You forgot the most important thing
你忘记了最重要的事情
Those keys of yours
你的那些钥匙
not enough
不够
And the last key?
最后一把钥匙呢？
you don't have that key
你没有那把钥匙
No matter how many doors you open
无论你打开多少扇门
You can't escape either
你也无法逃脱
that key
那把钥匙
Nishimura is not hanging on his waist
西村没有挂在腰上
He usually keeps it with his private key.
他通常用他的私钥保存它。
It's in his left trouser pocket
它在他的左裤兜里
Are you sure you have the ability to get the key?
你确定你有能力拿到钥匙吗？
really uncertain
真的不确定
Please tell me first how much money you can give me.
请先告诉我你能给我多少钱。
How much do you want
你想要多少
one thousand
一千
I don't have that much money
我没有那么多钱
Aren't you wasting your time here?
你这不是在浪费时间吗？
you have no money
你没有钱
What are you doing out there?
你在外面做什么？
Might as well stay here
还不如留在这里
Eat together
一起吃
Eight hundred
八百
All my property
我所有的财产
How about it
这个怎么样
do you recognize that key
你认识那把钥匙吗
The nose was cut off
鼻子被割掉了
I don't have it, sir.
我没有，先生。
I'm not that cruel
我没那么残忍
He said he didn't
他说他没有
He has it
他有它
Indeed there are
确实有
He has a knife in his hand
他手里拿着一把刀
Yeah
是的
sir
先生
There's something wrong with this guy's brain
这家伙脑子有问题
Do you think this is a knife?
你认为这是一把刀吗？
This is what I usually use to trim my nails.
这是我经常用来修剪指甲的。
There's no problem with this
这个没有问题
Yes, sir
是的先生
You can't trust him
你不能相信他
sir
先生
You must make the decision for me, sir.
你必须为我做出决定，先生。
you save me
你救我
Is this a knife?
这是刀吗？
Look
看
The nose is still on the face
鼻子还在脸上
Are you kidding me?
你在开玩笑吧？
do you want to die
你想死吗
Don't, don't
不要，不要
I'll help you
我会帮你
sir
先生
dream dream dream
梦梦梦
that
那
You're not talking about him
你不是在谈论他
Always loves to dig people’s eyes out
总是喜欢挖人的眼睛
Bite your ears?
咬耳朵？
I just had a dream
我刚刚做了一个梦
too real
太真实了
Be honest
说实话
If you make trouble again, I'll kill you
你要是再闹，我就杀了你
sir
先生
treat him well
善待他
Sorry to disturb your rest
抱歉打扰您休息
sorry
对不起
Get along with
取得进展
I don’t dare anymore. I don’t dare anymore.
我不敢了。我不敢了。
This key is divided into three parts
这个key分为三个部分
length of key
密钥长度
Equivalent to the total length of your index finger
相当于食指的总长度
length of key body
钥匙体长度
Equivalent to the first joint of the index finger
相当于食指的第一关节
and the length of the second joint
和第二个关节的长度
There is a third part
还有第三部分
The sawtooth part is square
锯齿部分是方形的
Grooves on three sides
三边有凹槽
Equilateral length
等边长度
One-third of your first knuckle
第一个指关节的三分之一
Don’t worry, I’ve remembered everything clearly.
别担心，我已经把一切都记得清清楚楚了。
Don't be too happy too early
别高兴得太早
What's wrong
怎么了
material for making keys
制作钥匙的材料
have nothing left
一无所有
no
不
There are so many hinges on this bed
这张床上有很多铰链
You've used it all
你都用过了
Do you really think that the materials I made earlier
你真的认为我之前做的材料
Is it a success every time?
每次都成功吗？
Available now
现在有空
It’s not that the thickness is not enough
不是厚度不够
Otherwise, it will be rusty
不然会生锈
What about wood?
木头呢？
Wood is too brittle
木头太脆
I can't bear the exertion at all
我根本无法承受这样的劳累
This should work
这应该有效
Mahogany
桃花心木
Definitely hard enough
绝对够难
If you carve along the wood grain
如果你沿着木纹雕刻
It shouldn't be a big problem
应该不是大问题
Mr. Yamashita
山下先生
Then I'll go home first
那我就先回家了
Since we are getting married
既然我们要结婚了
Just don’t call me Mr. Yamashita.
只是不要叫我山下先生。
OK
好的
Tonight's press conference
今晚的新闻发布会
I am very satisfied
我很满意
Are you tired too?
你也累吗？
Go home early and rest
早点回家休息
good
好的
The copper plate of border coins is in Wang Dapu's hands
边陲铜板在王大璞手中
He was anxious to escape
他急于逃跑
The copper plate must be handed over to the military commander
铜板必须交给军事指挥官
Just follow him
跟着他就行了
You can find the copper plate
你可以找到铜板
It surprised me that
让我惊讶的是
Jiang Zhao would do such a thing
江昭会做出这样的事
I think
我认为
Maybe you don't know him
也许你不认识他
Do not worry
不用担心
I will convince him
我会说服他
correct
正确的
Did Yamashita tell you about the Sugi Project?
山下告诉过你有关杉计划的事吗？
No
不
But Fujita, the driver at Yamashita, told me
但山下的司机藤田告诉我
Yamashita is working for the Empire of Japan
山下正在为日本帝国工作
do something great
做一些伟大的事情
how about you
你呢
What are your plans for the future?
你未来的计划是什么？
I really want to marry Yamashita
我真的很想嫁给山下
I've already planned it
我已经计划好了
Have you brought anything?
你带东西了吗？
Don't worry, it's colorless and odorless
别担心，它是无色无味的
Is it toxic enough?
毒性够大吗？
It's okay to poison a horse to death
毒死马也没关系
Lieutenant Commander Uchida promised me
内田少校答应过我
Can be alone with Mr. Jiang
可以和江先生单独相处
This skirt is still there
这条裙子还在
Why do you want to frame Chen Jiaping?
为什么要陷害陈家平？
It turns out you came to me because of this matter.
原来你是因为这件事才来找我的。
Why
为什么
this is politics
这就是政治
You do not understand
你不明白
I don’t understand politics
我不懂政治？？？
But I understand someone
但我理解一个人
You should have the minimum integrity and conscience
你应该有起码的诚信和良知
anyway
反正
No one should be framed
任何人都不应该被陷害
people who have helped you
帮助过你的人
Zuo Shuangtao asked you to come, right?
左双涛叫你来是吗？
Chen Jiaping was very helpful to me.
陈家平对我帮助很大。
After you return to Chongqing
返回重庆后
I once couldn't think about it
我曾经无法思考
If it weren't for Chen Jiaping
如果不是陈家平
I'm already dead
我已经死了
why didn't you tell me earlier
你为什么不早点告诉我
Chen Jiaping was imprisoned in a detention center by the Japanese
陈家平被日军关进看守所
Only if you change your confession
只要你改变你的坦白
Only then can we save him
只有这样我们才能救他
good
好的
I promise you
我答应你
You need to tell Uchida
你得告诉内田
The person who gave you the labor certificate is Zhao An
给你开劳工证的人是赵安
Zhao An is the real Five of Hearts
赵安才是真正的红心五人
Want to put the blame on Zhao An
想把责任推到赵安身上
Just relying on my confession
只依靠我的坦白
I'm afraid it's not enough
恐怕还不够
They have other plans
他们还有其他计划
All you have to do is say this
你所要做的就是这样说
Just think of it as the last thing you can do for me.
把它当作你能为我做的最后一件事吧。
one last thing
最后一件事
What do you mean
你是什​​么意思
When are you going to see Uchida?
你什么时候去见内田？
Noon
中午
Every day at noon
每天中午
Uchida will return to the Military Police Headquarters
内田将返回宪兵司令部
Then I'll see you again in the afternoon
那我下午再来看你
come to me again
再次来到我身边
I saw that Xinghualou’s mung bean cake is on the market again.
我看到杏花楼的绿豆糕又上市了。
I want to buy some and come over to eat with you
我想买一些过来和你一起吃
Uchida
内田
Will you be allowed to come to me again and again?
你可以一次又一次地来找我吗？
This is also the military police headquarters anyway.
反正这里也是宪兵司令部。
You can't escape either
你也无法逃脱
Isn't it?
不是吗？
yes
是的
This is the military police headquarters
这里是宪兵司令部
Can't escape
无法逃脱
do you remember
你是否记得
Have we taken a photo together before?
我们以前一起拍过照片吗？
You were also wearing this skirt that day
那天你也穿了这条裙子
the weather that day
那天的天气
also very good
也很好
Miss Hanlu
韩璐小姐
What a coincidence
多么巧合
you are here too
你也在这里
correct
正确的
congratulations
恭喜
What do you congratulate me on?
你祝贺我什么？
What does this mean
这是什么意思
Haven't you seen it all?
你还没有看到这一切吗？
Did you promise him?
你答应他了吗？
When you spoke, did you answer him?
当你说话的时候，你有回应他吗？
Yesterday they said they were going to execute you
昨天他们说要处决你
if i don't agree
如果我不同意
Who is Shanxia?
山霞是谁？
All I know is that Uchida is helping him
我只知道内田在帮助他
he has great power
他有很大的力量
Why didn't I think of it earlier?
为什么我没有早点想到呢？
Yamashita Takeo
山下武夫
He is the controller of Project Sugi
他是Project Sugi的控制者
he is the one
他就是那个
what are you going to do
你会怎样做
You have already bought the mung bean cake
你已经买了绿豆糕
What is this, what is this?
这是什么，这是什么？
you give me
你给我
Bring it over and show it to me
把它拿过来给我看
What's this
这是什么
Give me
给我吗
Poison?
毒？
Do you want to poison me to death?
你想毒死我吗？
You want to sprinkle it on mung bean cake
你想撒在绿豆糕上
Let me eat it and poison me to death, right?
让我吃下去毒死我吧？
yes
是的
I just want to poison you to death
我只想毒死你
But I don't just want to poison you
但我不只是想毒害你
I want to eat mung bean cake with you
我想和你一起吃绿豆糕
I'll die with you
我会和你一起死
you are crazy
你疯了
I'm not crazy
我没疯
I know very well what Yamashita Takeo's methods are.
我很清楚山下武夫的手段是什么。
He won't let you go
他不会让你走
He won't let me go either
他也不会让我走
He will use you as a weight to blackmail me.
他会拿你作为敲诈勒索的筹码。
the two of us
我们俩
The two of us forever
我们两个永远
Don't even think about getting rid of him
根本就别想摆脱他
you are really crazy
你真的疯了
I can't die, you know?
我不能死，你知道吗？
I have a mission
我有一个使命
I have to live well
我必须好好生活
I can't die with you
我不能和你一起死
Are you still alive like this?
你还这样活着吗？
You have to get me out
你必须带我出去
I have to get out of here
我必须离开这里
Takeo Yamashita is the controller of Project Sugi
山下武雄 (Takeo Yamashita) 是 Project Sugi 的控制者
he loves you so much
他非常爱你
You must have a way
你一定有办法
Asked him to let me out
请求他让我出去
did you mean
你的意思
Let me really marry Yamashita
让我真的嫁给山下
to exchange for your freedom
来换取你的自由
If we are still together in the future
如果未来我们还在一起
you
你
Can you just make a little sacrifice?
你能做出一点小小的牺牲吗？
did you mean
你的意思
I want to keep Yamashita’s dirty hands off
我不想让山下的脏手离开
touch me again
再次触摸我
Will you taint me again?
你还要再玷污我吗？
Hanlu, listen to me
韩璐，听我说
I don't want to hear you anymore
我不想再听你说话了
every word you say
你说的每一句话
They are all insulting me
他们都在侮辱我
They are all insulting our love
他们都在侮辱我们的爱情
I beg you
我求求你
help me again
再次帮助我
How about the last time?
上次怎么样？
Help you once
帮你一次
Then who am I?
那我是谁？
After I go out
我出去之后
I
我
After I destroyed the Shan Project
当我摧毁了掸族计划之后
you are like me
你和我一样
All are heroes
都是英雄
hero
英雄
Do you think I want to be a hero?
你以为我想成为英雄吗？
Since you don't help me
既然你不帮我
I just insist
我只是坚持
Chen Jiaping is the Five of Hearts
陈家平是红心五人
You are really despicable
你实在是太卑鄙了
Don’t you want to help Chen Jiaping?
难道你不想帮助陈家平吗？
Don't you want to save him?
你不想救他吗？
OK
好的
no problem
没问题
Get me out first
先带我出去
I want to get Yamashita Takeo
我想要山下武夫
After hand-signed release order
手签放行单后
I immediately changed my mind
我立刻改变了主意
do you know
你知道吗
Yamashita Takeo
山下武夫
He is very gentle to me on the surface
他表面上对我很温柔
But he is actually a complete pervert
但他其实是个彻头彻尾的变态
We are all adults
我们都是成年人
I do not care
我不在乎
You, you are shameless
你你无耻啊
How long until it arrives
还要等多久才能到达
It's going to be there in less than five minutes.
不到五分钟就会到。
parking
停車處
Parking Parking
停车位 停车位
What happened to Captain Zhao?
赵队长怎么了？
fine
美好的
I'll put some water in
我会放一些水进去
Wait for me
等我
Tom
汤姆
I'm going to discuss something with Trunk
我要和 Trunk 讨论一些事情
You go first and drive quickly
你先走，开快点
Captain, it's almost too late
队长，已经太晚了
It's almost time
时间差不多了
That's too late
太晚了
Let me tell the car behind me something
让我告诉后面的车一些事情
Follow
跟随
It's almost too late
已经太晚了
Follow quickly
快速关注
Go, go, go
去！去！去
What happened to the captain?
船长怎么了？
keep up keep up keep up
跟上 跟上 跟上
Chief Uchida
内田长官
cotton yarn
棉线团
Please convey my gratitude to Mr. Yamashita for me.
请代我转达对山下先生的谢意。
Mr. Yamashita said
山下先生说
This is his first time
这是他第一次
Also the last time
也是最后一次
Let go of your enemies with your own hands
用自己的双手放开你的敌人
Since Mr. Yamashita gives me such face,
既然山下先生给了我这样的面子，
Then I will also give Mr. Yamashita a gift.
那么我也会给山下先生一份礼物。
what gift
什么礼物
a truth
一个事实
you say
你说
In fact, Chen Jiaping
In fact, Chen Jiaping
Not the five of hearts
不是红心五
I deliberately put the blame on him
我故意把责任推到他身上
why did you do this
你为什么要这么做
because before i
因为在我之前
I heard that his relationship with Han Lu is very ambiguous.
听说他和韩露的关系很暧昧。
But what I didn't expect was
但没想到的是
She betrayed me
她背叛了我
It’s not Chen Jiaping
这不是陈家平吗
But Yamashita Takeo
但山下武夫
So there is no need for me to frame Chen Jiaping
所以我没必要陷害陈家平
You said it before
你之前说过
Now suddenly changed his mind
现在突然改变了主意
Do you think I would believe it?
你觉得我会相信吗？
Do you believe it or not?
你信不信？
Is it important to me?
对我来说重要吗？
It's the cold dew that asks for something from me
是寒露向我索要什么
I just told you the truth
我只是告诉你真相
As for whether you want to execute Chen Jiaping in the future?
至于以后是否要处决陈家平？
That's your own business
那是你自己的事
If Chen Jiaping is not the Five of Hearts
如果陈家平不是红心五人
Who is the real Five of Hearts?
谁才是真正的红心五人？
and you
你呢
You can only let your men
你只能让你的男人
Put a gun to my head again and ask
再次用枪指着我的头问
Maybe I'll tell you
也许我会告诉你
I know
我知道
Mr. Jiang is probably just pretending to be afraid of death.
江先生大概只是装怕死吧。
The information you told us
您告诉我们的信息
seems important
似乎很重要
In fact, you have already made up your mind
其实你已经下定决心了
We can't find the recipe or the copper plate at all
我们根本找不到配方或铜板
So it doesn't hurt to tell us, right?
所以告诉我们也没什么坏处，对吧？
Who is the Five of Hearts?
红心五人是谁？
Such important information
如此重要的信息
you won't tell us
你不会告诉我们
But don't worry
但不用担心
I'll find out
我会查明真相的
Mr. Jiang
Mr. Jiang
We did not reach a consensus in this cooperation
这次合作我们没有达成共识
Very sorry
很抱歉
But if there are regrets, there are expectations
但有遗憾就有期待
We have a long way to go
我们还有很长的路要走
I'm also looking forward to it
我也很期待
Meeting Mr. Uchida again
再次见到内田先生
But I will never give it to you again
但我再也不会给你了
A chance to put a gun to my head
有机会用枪指着我的头
I don't think so
我不这么认为
Where is Zhao An?
赵安在哪里？
I have no idea
我不知道
I ask you where is Zhao An?
我问你赵安在哪儿？
Chief Uchida, I really don’t know.
内田局长，我真的不知道。
Captain Zhao was always in Tom's car.
赵队长总是在汤姆的车里。
I really don't know, Chief Uchida
我真的不知道 内田队长
After Captain Zhao finished urinating, he asked me to leave first.
赵队长尿完后，让我先走。
Then he wanted to discuss something with Chen Shugan
然后他想跟陈树干商量点事情
No
不
Captain Zhao didn't get into my car
赵队长没有上我的车
He told us to leave quickly
他叫我们快点离开
He got into the car behind
他上了后面的车
I really do not know
我真的不知道
Chief Uchida
内田长官
we catch someone
我们抓住某人
Let him explain the situation
让他说明一下情况
look
看
bring people here
带人来这里
Hou Si
Hou Si
Say it again what you just told me
把你刚才告诉我的话再说一遍
Who is the buyer of this batch of cotton yarn?
这批棉纱的买家是谁？
Boss Zhou
周老板
Which Zhou boss
哪个周老板
It's Du Yuesheng in Chongqing
It's Du Yuesheng in Chongqing
That Tongti company
那个通体公司
Boss Zhou Qingsen specializes in Jiangsu, Zhejiang and Shanghai areas
Boss Zhou Qingsen specializes in Jiangsu, Zhejiang and Shanghai areas
It is said
据说
He allocated a lot of money
他拨了很多钱
Can get scarce supplies
可以获得稀缺物资
So the buyer is the Chongqing government
所以买家是重庆市政府
I'm just an errand boy
我只是个跑腿的
How did you know about this batch of cotton yarn?
您是如何知道这批棉纱的？
Boss Zhou told me
周老板告诉我的
He said over there in Shanghai
他说在上海那边
Is there someone who can get the best cotton yarn?
有人能买到最好的棉纱吗？
who's that person
那个人是谁
He didn't say it directly
他没有直接说
But once
但有一次
I heard him call that guy
我听到他打电话给那个人
I heard that he seemed to be from the military command
听说他好像是军部的
What's the code name?
代号是什么？
five of hearts
红心五
Chief Uchida
内田长官
This is called Chen Shugan
这叫陈树干
He is Zhao An’s confidant
他是赵安的心腹
Since he is a confidant
既然他是知己
You don't know
你不知道
Your Captain Zhao is the Five of Hearts of the military commander, right?
你们赵队长是武将的红心五人吧？
impossible
不可能的
This is absolutely impossible
这是绝对不可能的
Chief Uchida
内田长官
There's no way he doesn't know
他不可能不知道
I really don't know anything
我真的什么都不知道
Chief Uchida, I really don’t know.
内田局长，我真的不知道。
you believe me
你相信我
What do you say
你怎么说
Why doesn’t Boss Zhou come?
周老板怎么没来？
I do not know either
我也不知道
We agreed to meet here at five o'clock
我们约定五点钟在这里见面
Could it be that he discovered in advance that there was an ambush here?
难道他提前发现这里有埋伏？
Run away first
先逃走
I see
我懂了
I understand, Chief Uchida.
我明白了，内田队长。
Zhao An deceived us all
赵安欺骗了我们所有人
He deliberately let us continue here
他故意让我们在这里继续
Just to distract you
只是为了分散你的注意力
He had time to escape
他有时间逃跑
Chief Uchida, this matter has nothing to do with me.
内田队长，这件事与我无关。
I really do not know
我真的不知道
What you said seems to make sense
你说的好像有道理
Chief Uchida
内田长官
Please spare my life
请饶我一命
spare my life
饶我一命
I will be a cow and a horse for you from now on
今后我为你做牛做马
As long as you don't kill me
只要你不杀我
Then why don't I think
那我为什么不认为
You and Zhao An are accomplices
你和赵安是同谋
You lead us away
你带我们走
So that he can cover his escape.
这样他就可以掩护自己逃跑。
No
不
I don't
我不
Shuyun
Shuyun
Why did you come?
你为什么来？
problem occurs
出现问题
What's wrong
怎么了
you
你
Why are you carrying such a big box?
你为什么提这么大的箱子？
Here are all my belongings
这是我所有的物品
What's the meaning
什么意思
The days when I followed the Japanese
追随日本人的日子
Completely over
彻底结束
Thanks to my bright brain
感谢我聪明的大脑
Escaped
逃脱
Otherwise you won't be able to see me
不然你就看不到我了
Chen Shugan them
陈树干他们
died
死了
So what should we do now?
那么我们现在应该做什么呢？
I'll go to Pudong with you
我和你一起去浦东
Let's hide for a while
我们躲一会儿吧
Then find a way to leave Shanghai
然后想办法离开上海
What about after that?
那之后呢？
Will we keep escaping like this from now on?
今后我们还要这样逃避吗？
You are my only support now
你是我现在唯一的依靠
You can't let me live like this
你不能让我这样生活
Shuyun
Shuyun
Believe me
相信我
There's enough money in the box to last us a lifetime
盒子里的钱足够我们用一辈子
I'll take you to Hong Kong
我带你去香港
let's buy a big house
我们买一栋大房子吧
I'll go there to invest and do some business.
我要去那里投资，做点生意。
Our life won't be bad
我们的生活不会太糟糕
By the time
到......的时候
I will organize a grand wedding for you
我会为你举办一场盛大的婚礼
Then you give me a big fat boy
那你给我一个大胖子
We are a family of three
我们是一家三口
No need to worry about food or clothing
无需担心食物或衣服
live a good life
过上美好的生活
go to Hong Kong
去香港
Hongkong
香港
Went to his
去了他的
Imperial Army National Army Japanese
皇军国民军日本人
Get out
出去
I have been the grandson of the Japanese for so many years
我当日本人的孙子这么多年
Why do I
我为什么会
I just want to make a lot of money
我只想赚很多钱
I live my life
我过我的生活
I let you live a good life with me
我让你和我一起过上美好的生活
Right
正确的
Shuyun
Shuyun
You have been suffering with me during this time
这段时间你陪我一起受苦
I'll replenish it for you later
稍后我会为你补充
Let's go to the ferry right now
我们现在就去渡轮吧
Wait a moment
稍等
What's wrong
怎么了
I still have something to get
我还有东西要得到
what is this
这是什么
Some of my gold and silver are so soft
我的一些金银很软
There are also some cheongsams I just made.
还有一些我刚做的旗袍。
where is it
它在哪里
I'm hiding in the ruined temple opposite
我躲在对面的破庙里
Shuyun
Shuyun
Come in Shuyun
Come in Shuyun
come in and save me
进来救我
Shuyun
Shuyun
Zhao An
Zhao An
What are you doing with my wife?
你和我老婆做什么？
I'm here
我在这
Luo Guanqun
Luo Guanqun
why are you here
你为什么在这
my wife is here
我妻子在这里
why can't i be here
为什么我不能在这里
Where's Shuyun?
淑云在哪儿？
she's next to me
她在我旁边
Shuyun
Shuyun
Say something to Captain Zhao
跟赵队长说句话
Don't be afraid
别害怕
Let the past go by
让过去过去吧
You behaved very well today
你今天表现得很好
Luo Guanqun, your uncle
Luo Guanqun, your uncle
You coerced Zhang Shuyun
You coerced Zhang Shuyun
Shuyun
Shuyun
Zhao An
Zhao An
Stop talking nonsense here
别在这里废话了
You forced me from beginning to end
从头到尾都是你逼我的
Shuyun
Shuyun
I'm sincere to you
我对你是真心的
Have you forgotten how Luo Guanqun beat you?
你忘了罗冠群是怎么打你的吗？
Zhao An
Zhao An
You don't believe anyone
你不相信任何人
I just believe in women
我只相信女人
But it’s because of women
但这是因为女人
lied to you
对你撒谎了
you have to die
你必须死
he was angry
他生气了
buried him
埋葬了他
Shuyun
Shuyun
Don't listen
别听
Don't listen to Luo Guanqun lie to you
Don't listen to Luo Guanqun lie to you
You just buried me
你刚刚埋葬了我
He won't let you go either
他也不会让你走
Did you hear Shuyun?
你听到舒云的声音了吗？
Shuyun
Shuyun
Luo Guanqun, stop it
Luo Guanqun, stop it
I didn't bury you
我没有埋葬你
It was Shuyun who buried you
是淑云埋葬了你
Shuyun
Shuyun
He is lying to you Shuyun
他在骗你 舒云
come on
快点
Luo Guanqun
Luo Guanqun
Please let me go
请放我走
I have money
我有钱
I'll give you all the money
我会把所有的钱都给你
Look, that box is full of money.
看，那个箱子里装满了钱。
this is the key
这是关键
Give
给
I throw it up
我把它扔了
Look at the money in the box
看看盒子里的钱
for you
为你
Zhao An
Zhao An
I'd like to see
我倒要看看
How much money have you made in the past few years?
过去几年你赚了多少钱？
Zhao An
Zhao An
You really didn't disappoint me
你果然没有让我失望
Luo Guanqun will give it to you
罗冠群送给你
Shuyun
Shuyun
I beg you
我求求你
Stop pouring dirt, Shuyun
别再泼脏水了，舒云
You have to save me Shuyun
你一定要救救我舒云
Shuyun, look inside the box
淑云，看看盒子里面
I have a gift for you Shuyun
我有礼物给你 舒云
Last time we saw it together
上次我们一起看过
I want to surprise you
我想给你一个惊喜
Take a look at Shuyun
看看舒云
This is the gift Captain Zhao bought for you
这是赵队长给你买的礼物
How do you want to deal with it
你想怎么处理
Qun Ge
Qun Ge
I was wrong, Brother Qun
群哥我错了
Spare my life, Brother Qun
群哥饶我一命
I, Zhao An, am finished
我赵安完了
I can't stay in Shanghai any longer
我不能再留在上海了
I go
我去
Qun Ge
Qun Ge
Spare my life, Brother Qun
群哥饶我一命
I was wrong
我错了
I shouldn't seek your position
我不应该寻求你的立场
I shouldn't steal your goods
我不应该偷你的东西
I shouldn't have any bad thoughts about Mrs. Luo
我不应该对洛太太有什么不好的想法
I beg you
我求求你
Spare my life
饶我一命
I beg you, Brother Qun
群哥求你了
Zhao An
Zhao An
You also have today
你也有今天
Shuyun
Shuyun
I am sincere to you Shuyun
我对你是真心的 淑云
I really want to take you away
我真的很想带你走
Break his spell and break the net
打破他的咒语并打破网
Lift the barrier of death and disaster
解除死亡和灾难的障碍
Save all injustice and suffering
拯救一切不公与苦难
Clean, bright and more auspicious
干净、明亮、更吉祥
Break his spell and break the net
打破他的咒语并打破网
Lift the barrier of death and disaster
解除死亡和灾难的障碍
rescue
救援
Zhao An
Zhao An
Huangquan Road
Huangquan Road
I'll give you a ride
我送你一程
I am sincerely Shuyun
我真诚的淑云
I want to live a good life with you
我想和你一起过上美好的生活
I want to take you away
我想带你走
buy a big house
买一栋大房子
give birth
生
I want to give you a good life
我想给你美好的生活
All squatted
全部蹲下
Manager Luo
Manager Luo
Zhao An's men
Zhao An's men
Except for those who were arrested last night
除了昨晚被捕的人
All the rest is here
其余的都在这里
Zhao An colluded with the military
赵安与军方勾结
Do you know the evidence?
你知道证据吗？
It’s not a matter of one or two days.
这不是一两天的事。
You must know a thing or two
你必须知道一两件事
If there is a problem, there is evidence
有问题就有证据
Report everything to me
向我报告一切
If you cover up and conceal
如果你掩盖和隐瞒
The consequences will be the same as him
后果会和他一样
large spoon
大勺子
exist
存在
if they don't say
如果他们不说
Get my teeth punched
让我的牙齿被打一拳
If you don't say it again
如果你不再说一遍
Take out your heart for me
为我掏出你的心
yes
是的
How about it
这个怎么样
Do you understand?
你明白吗？
Who wants to report and expose Zhao An?
谁要举报揭露赵安？
Now give you a chance
现在给你一个机会
I know
我知道
I said
我说
I know too
我也知道
I also said
我也说过
Don't worry
不用担心
Come one by one
一一来
You speak first
你先说话
Manager Luo
Manager Luo
Where do you think Captain Zhao fled to?
你猜赵队长逃到哪里去了？
how could I know
我怎么知道
I estimate that he is probably dead.
我估计他很可能已经死了。
what do you think
你怎么认为
I also accidentally heard it a few days ago
我也是前几天无意中听到的
Captain Zhao is in his office
赵队长在办公室
Planning an escape
计划逃跑
Manager Luo, don’t worry
罗经理，别担心
I understand
我明白
See many things with your eyes
用眼睛看到很多东西
Put it in the stomach
放进肚子里
But it must not leak out of your mouth
但一定不能从嘴里漏出来
Qian Xiucai
Qian Xiucai
I know you helped me with this matter
我知道你帮我解决了这件事
I remember it
我记得
By the way, Manager Luo
对了，罗经理
Have you read the Chronicles of the Eastern Zhou Dynasties?
你读过《东周纪事》吗？
What about Wei State?
魏国呢？
There was a janitor named Hou Ying
从前有一个看门人，名叫侯英。
Have a strategy in mind
心中有一个策略
But hide it
但隐藏它
Until I met Mr. Xinling
直到遇见心陵先生
Only by oneself can one see the virtuous
只有自己才能看到贤德
And finally became Lord Xinling
最后成为信陵君
Offered a plan to steal the talisman to save Zhao
献计盗符救赵
Protected Wei State
保护魏国
what do you mean
你是什​​么意思
without
没有
nothing
没有什么
That is, if Manager Luo is interested, he would like to read it.
就是说，罗经理如果有兴趣，就想看。
Words from the Chronicles of the States of the Eastern Zhou Dynasty
东周国记词
I can lend it to you anytime
我可以随时借给你
Qian Xiucai
Qian Xiucai
you
你
what is your real name
你的真实姓名是什么
Qian Chengyi
Qian Chengyi
sun gongyi pawn
sun gongyi pawn
The one who becomes one in the end
最终成为一体的人
Manager Luo
Manager Luo
I really didn't expect that
我真的没想到
Zhao An is the real Five of Hearts
赵安才是真正的红心五人
yes
是的
I didn’t expect that the five hearts were hidden so deeply.
没想到五颗心藏得这么深。
Zhao An fled in fear of crime
赵安畏罪潜逃
This further proves our Jiaping’s innocence.
这进一步证明了我们家平的清白。
Jiang Zhaoguo suddenly overturned his confession
蒋兆国突然翻盘
Saying that the Five of Hearts is not Chen Jiaping
说红心五不是陈家平
Do you think this is strange?
你觉得这很奇怪吗？
What's so strange about this?
这有什么奇怪的呢？
Doesn't he always hold grudges?
他不是一直记仇吗？
Are Jia Ping and Han Lu close?
家平和韩露关系好吗？
Only intentionally framed
只是故意陷害
Since everyone has come to the rescue
既然大家都来救援了
He had no choice but to tell the truth
他别无选择，只能说出真相
Am I right
我对吗
five of hearts
红心五
Four of clubs
俱乐部四
You said we should go find Chief Uchida this time
你说这次我们应该去找内田局长
Can you bring Jia Ping out smoothly?
你能顺利把贾平带出来吗？
The evidence is complete
证据齐全
but
但
It’s hard to say Japanese people
日本人很难说
Chen Jiaping
Chen Jiaping
It's hard to say
很难说
It's been several days
已经好几天了
There is no news about Jia Ping
还没有贾平的消息
Imprisoned in that terrible place
被囚禁在那个可怕的地方
I really don't know what will happen
我真的不知道会发生什么
What book are you reading?
你在读什么书？
The Japanese can't even understand a loyal traitor like you
日本人连你这样的忠诚汉奸都无法理解
All caught
全部抓获
So blind
如此盲目
at the beginning
一开始
I thought about climbing over the wall and getting out.
我想过翻墙出去。
But later I discovered
但后来我发现
Totally impossible
完全不可能
Can you see the entire building clearly?
你能清楚地看到整栋大楼吗？
The first floor is where Japanese activities take place.
一楼是进行日本活动的地方。
There is a canteen on the far right
最右边有一个食堂
There's a back door leading outside
有一个后门通向外面
And we have to go down to the first floor through the second floor
我们必须通过二楼下到一楼
You have to go through three iron gates first
首先要经过三道铁门
There are four more iron gates to pass behind.
后面还有四道铁门要经过。
to escape
逃离
That's the escape route
这就是逃生路线
Remember clearly
记得清楚
The show starts at eight o'clock
演出八点开始
A total of eight programs
共有八个节目
If you want to escape
如果你想逃脱
Must escape before the show ends
必须在演出结束前逃脱